Zoe T: My name's Zoe.
I am mum to Phillip, who is nearly
22 and Louie who is 18 next week.
Phillip has a diagnosis of
autism and Louie doesn't.
I am a widow.
I live in Oldham and I run Bright Future
School for children with autism, which is
in Greenfield, which is about 10 minutes
drive from here, which I set up in 2010
with my late husband because we couldn't
find anywhere - well, I say we, the local
authority couldn't find anywhere, a school
that was suitable to meet Phillip's needs.
And at that point we had just
starting taking part in an autism
intervention called Relationship
Development Intervention, which made
a massive difference to our lives
and our ability to understand Phillip
and his ability to engage with us.
Because that worked on the core
difficulties at the heart of autism
and because the autism was, as far as
we could see, the main thing that was
the obstacle for Phillip to engage in
education and with the wider world.
We wanted a school placement
that would embed those sorts of
principles into the school day.
We couldn't find one, so we ended
up setting up our own school.